{
    "subject": "resource/Paulo_Moura",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Brazil",
    "human_readable": "Paulo Moura was born in Brazil.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9308138489723206,
            "question": "Where was Paulo Moura born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8990708589553833,
            "question": "Is Paulo Moura Brazilian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7201563119888306,
            "question": "What country is Paulo Moura from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.592685878276825,
            "question": "What is Paulo Moura known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5347504615783691,
            "question": "Does Paulo Moura have a family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4096117913722992,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Paulo Moura?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39429014921188354,
            "question": "Where might Paulo Moura live now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.230686753988266,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Brazil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15672235190868378,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Brazil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1339133083820343,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Brazil?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paulo Moura was born in Brazil.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6897_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the culture like in Brazil?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6897_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from Brazil?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6897_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Paulo Moura live now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6897_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6897_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Paulo Moura was born on July 15, 1932, in Brazil. Therefore, the statement \"Paulo Moura was born in Brazil\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}